The Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series Begins
This is Mai Handa.
And this is Hanon from Kyushu Girls' Club.
Pleased to meet you.
This interview was recorded on June 3rd at Harajuku LOUIDE
We recorded it the day after Tokyo Nighttime Land vol.2, which was held on June 3rd at Llewd in Harajuku.
It's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who couldn't make it to the event because of the capacity of about 150 people, so I'd like to explain a little bit about what kind of event it was.
The performers of this volume 2 are NORUNA-chan, Kana-Marima, Kana-chan Yasumori, Wakamori, and Kana-chan Harima.
Kana Haruma, Waka Yasumori, Hana Kojima, Rina Tanaka, Saho Tanaka, Lulie Aoi, and for the first time, I'm Haru, and for the first time from a group other than the stars, I'm Kanochan
Kano-chan.
Yesterday, we had nine performers here, but Kano-chan was the first person from an office other than StarLast to perform at Tokyo Nighttime Land itself.
The first. The first.
But yesterday, when I heard that you came from a place other than Starrlast, it was the first time I heard that you thought you might have been bullied there.
I think I might have been on the good side of the line, but I was laughing so hard on the bad side.
Everybody laughed.
No way. Yes, that's right. But, you know, it wasn't like that at all. Oh, thank God!
Everyone was so kind, so kind that I was able to express my ideas. Thank God! I think I'm really going to be bullied until it starts.
That's why I'm extremely shy. Really? I was really surprised when I heard that.
But I knew that if I showed my shyness here, I would never fit in. So when I get stuck in a conversation, I need to find a way to cut through it.
I think I search youtube every day to learn how to cut through the clutter and how to talk with people I don't know before I meet them.
I also thought it would be easier to talk to people if I knew them by watching all their backout idols,
I've watched a lot of Backout Idol, and I know everyone pretty well in advance. I was really scared of the preparation.
I was really scared, because everyone talked to me so much during the first day of rehearsal. That's right.
I learned from my seniors how to treat each other, so we are all very friendly with each other.
I'm famous for my peacefulness. I am also famous for my peace. KANO-chan's manager just showed me a video of the day before the first day of rehearsals.
She showed me the video from the day before the first day of rehearsal,
It was a video of KANO-chan sitting and crying in the middle of a normal town.
It's okay.
It's still early. We can walk together for a little while longer.
Everyone will be there.
KANO, I'll be a little far away.
I'll wait for you without making a move.
That's right. The day before, there was an off-line meeting in Yamaguchi Prefecture.
We had an off-line meeting at a famous restaurant called High Karat Yokocho, and on the way back to the car, I asked a member to hold my hand,
The members were holding my hand on the way back to the car, and they were talking to me like it was finally tomorrow,
I was holding his hand on the way back to the car, and he told me to call him no matter what happened, even if it was a trivial matter,
The thread became normal.
I was like, "Wow!
He was so kind to me.
Right then and there, she cried like a little kid.
I wonder what it would have been like if she had been a child.
Everyone gathered around and said, "Oh, my God!
We can still walk together a little longer.
Are you going to finish the grouping yet?
I don't know,
I think he must have been very anxious to come in alone in an office where all the other children were in the same place,
I'm sure you must have had a lot of worries,
I'm sure you must have had a lot to worry about, but you blended in so quickly that I couldn't tell that you were shy at all,
My first impression of Kamo-chan was that she didn't have a very friendly voice,
I think it was a great success.
I did my research and I think it paid off.
I remember the first time I talked with MayuMayu.
We were on the same elly time.
Yes, that's right.
She was so friendly.
I was so happy.
I was the one who was always talking to other people.
She really jumped in by herself,
He didn't show any worry or anxiety at all and ran through to the end,
I thought he was a really serious guy.
I was thinking about him throughout this period.
I'm very happy. Thank you very much.
We had about a week of lessons during the night.
There was a period of rehearsal lessons,
We decided to look back on the lessons a little bit,
I would like to talk about my impressions of each member and some episodes from the lessons.
Did you meet any of the members of this Diet before you came here?
I was on the Gig Takahashi 2 tour,
I was with Ohkubo Ohisa-san,
I also toured with Rena Naito on the Gig Takahashi 2 tour,
I also had a chance to talk with Mushroom Yasumori,
I had talked with Yasumori Mushroom, but I didn't really have that many chances to interact with them.
There are very few people that I talk to on a one-on-one basis.
Even if you meet people in a group or say hello, you don't get to talk to them one-on-one.
That's the beauty of this event.
I was very happy to be able to get to know each other so well.
I think it takes a lot of courage to do that on your first day,
He said he wanted to set up a video for every lesson, every day at rehearsal,
I asked if I could take a video with them.
I thought it would be a great way to get to know everyone a little better,
I was determined to do that, too.
I was really impressed by the high level of sensitivity.
It was high to begin with, but that was already great.
Thank you very much.
I was really surprised at how much they were doing.
I was really surprised,
Kaon, the timing of our first lesson together on the first day,
The timing of the reading and the voice training?
Yes.
We did the reading and voice training together,
I was doing the vocals, and while everyone else was making lyric cards and such,
I was the only one who had a notebook out,
I saw him open the notebook and sing from it,
I thought, "What? I thought, "What?
I'm the type of person who writes notes,
When I heard the song, I wrote down the lyrics myself,
I told him that it would be easier if we had a meeting in between so I could write down the lyrics,
Basil!
The members who play the lyrics are all very serious.
They are all really serious,Really, everyone is serious,
I do quite a bit.
There are some who do and some who write lyrics on lyric cards,
Some of them are writing lyrics,
I think most of the members are very serious.
There are a lot of good kids. Really.
They look at their sleeves and do things like this.
In my mind, I was doing it while looking up my sleeve,
Thank you.
I mean, I've been to festivals, like Stada's, or Stadustplanet's, for that matter, the whole Stadustplanet festival,
We all had rehearsals together,
You said that the rehearsals for this event were different from the rehearsals for the stadas and the girls' roles,
Yes, that's right. I was afraid of that, too,
The common sense of the female roles and the common sense of the stadia are different, aren't they?
It makes me scared.
So, the common sense that I thought I had,
I was afraid that they would think, "What the hell is this guy doing?
I was afraid that people might think what I thought I was doing,
But there is nothing I can do to find out.
But you can't even look it up. I feel like I'm watching everything,
I feel like I'm watching everything.
But I don't want to be too dyed in the wool,
I wanted to show a little of the color of a female actor,
So I decided to keep it as it is as much as possible.
I tried to keep it as it was in the end,
I can see that you really have the ability to handle it,
Really?
I can see that you can change the choreography and remember it immediately.
He does that quite a bit. Even the female roles.
Did you get used to it?
I had a solid foundation, a solid base.
I had a solid base, so I may have been trained in that area.
I had something that lived on in my idol activities,
I had something to live by in my idol activities.
That's why I was able to join the Kyushu Girls,
I was able to apply my experience in this way to the Stada office as well,
I was able to make the most of my experience,
I was able to make the most of my experience at Studer's office,
I was also impressed by the role of the girls.
I thought there were many people who came to this concert who came to like Hanae-chan a lot.
I saw it too.
Also, we performed all 11 songs this time.
And the play and so on.
All of them were cover songs.
Were there any songs you wanted to sing out of the 11 songs?
Before this event, I was asked in advance if there was a song I wanted to sing. I was asked before the event, "Which song would you like to sing?
I wanted to sing my prettiest part,
I also sent NotEqual B's song,
I also sent NotEqual B's song, Mahorod Asterisk, which is one of my favorite songs,
I recommended Mahrod.
I see.
I'm glad.
I love it.
That, when I heard the song I do,
I was so happy because it was so perfect.
It was the cutest part of me.
It was so cute.
I was really cute.
I used to dance to it on TikTok.
I thought it was a condensed version of the cuteness that Hanae-chan has,
I was watching the monitor in the back of the stage,
It was a cute song.
It was so cute, I was really just a watarik.
But the "kyun".
Kyun, too.
Kyun had a lot of cute songs.
There were a lot of cute songs.
And you sang solo, too.
That's right. This secret bass was the first time I was asked to sing solo,
I wanted to sing a solo at this Studio48-sponsored event.
I was too nervous, right? Then.
I was nervous when I first heard it,
But the lyrics of this song have amazing sad lyrics,
It's a song with the same tension all the way through,
I wondered how I should sing it so that everyone could feel it,
I was thinking about it a lot,
I sang this secret bass song thinking about the members of Joshiryoku.
There are so many members.
The eye pieces and everything is great.
I'm sure the people who came to this event and are watching this video will like it.
It's really full of charm.
Thank you very much.
When I said "Thank you very much" when I sang the song,
Thank you too.
Why?
I had a lot of anxiety, and yet here I was,
I had a lot of anxiety,
And you sang alone at this concert,
I really missed her a lot,
Really?
I was really in love with her,
But I feel like I grew up.
I think I grew up after this stage.
I had a lot of experiences that I could only have in various places.
But we were working together at the magic place, and then practicing together as a group after the lesson.
Afterwards, we would go out for dinner with other members who had free time,
It was really fun.
Without that kind of opportunity, we wouldn't have been able to talk one-on-one,
I felt like we were able to form bonds that were only possible because of this event,
When the event was over, I felt that we were able to form a great bond,I felt like we had done a great job, and when it was over at the end,
Before the concert, the nine of us worked together on the engine, and after the concert, we thanked everyone for their hard work.
I was sad. I was really sad.
I was really sad.
I thought I couldn't do it anymore.
It was really fun.
I want to tour all over Japan.
I want to go to Kyushu and Osaka.
That's how much fun I had.
Well, it looks like it's time for me to go,
The second part of the dialogue will be released tomorrow as well, so please take a look.
Please watch it.
Thank you very much.